

# **GUILHERME FRANCO**

**%** 917716006

#### O DETAILS O

<u>^</u>

#### **PROFILE**

917716006 gfguilherme1@gmail.com

# O SKILLS O

Java

Supercollider

SQL

Microsoft Office

Management Skills

Communication Skills

IT Project Management

# O Languages O

English

Spasnish

Portuguese

My relationship with the tech world started at a very young age, having received my first computer when I was 8 years old. At the time, I only used it to play video games but later that passion continued until high school when I started to have programming disciplines. During my high school years, I realized that I liked programming, but I would like to merge it with the world of marketing and management. For this very reason I went looking for a course that brought together these three worlds. And here I am! Being also a big fan of music events, I intend to take a Masters in Management and Event Planning, in order to connect all these worlds that I love so much.

#### **EMPLOYMENT HISTORY**

#### Internship at Do It Better!, Lisbon

February 2015 – March 2015

Computer Maintenance

#### Internship at Ok Medical, Birkirkara (Malta)

April 2016 - May 2016

Developing a task-sharing application for the employees

# Internship at Science4You, Lisbon

May 2016 - June 2016

Development of an application of statistics for the company. Computer Maintenance

# Summer Animations at Junta de Freguesia de Carnide, Lisbon

August 2018 - August 2020



#### **EDUCATION**

#### EQF level 4, Escola Digital, Lisbon

October 2013 - July 2016

Técnico de Gestão e Programação de Sistemas Informáticos

# EQF level 6, Universidade Lusófona de Humanidades e Tecnologias, Lisbon

September 2019 - Present

Computer Science and Business Management